{"bug":[{"level":"1","type":"bug","question":"I have six legs and can often be found crawling on the ground. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚶‍♀️ I have more legs than you do."},{"text":"🐛 I am smaller than a dog."},{"text":"🐜 I am a type of insect."}],"options":[{"label":"A Bird","isCorrect":false},{"label":"An Ant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Cat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"bug","question":"I fly around and make honey. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐝 I live in a hive."},{"text":"🍯 I make something sweet."},{"text":"🌼 I visit flowers."}],"options":[{"label":"A Butterfly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Bee","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Spider","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"bug","question":"I start as a caterpillar and turn into something beautiful that flies. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌈 I have colorful wings."},{"text":"🌱 I eat leaves when I'm young."},{"text":"🦋 I go through a big change called metamorphosis."}],"options":[{"label":"A Ladybug","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Butterfly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Grasshopper","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"bug","question":"I am red with black spots and considered lucky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐞 I am a small beetle."},{"text":"🍀 Some people believe I bring good fortune."},{"text":"⚫ I have dots on my back."}],"options":[{"label":"A Beetle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Ladybug","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Firefly","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"bug","question":"I make a sticky web to catch my dinner. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🕸️ My home is made of silk."},{"text":"🕷️ I have eight legs."},{"text":" 🐛 I eat insects."}],"options":[{"label":"A Spider","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Fly","isCorrect":false},{"label":"An Earthworm","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"bug","question":"I hop around and have strong legs. I'm known for my jumping ability. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌿 I like to live in grassy areas."},{"text":"🎶 I can make a chirping sound."},{"text":"🦵 My legs help me jump very high."}],"options":[{"label":"A Cricket","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Grasshopper","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Centipede","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"bug","question":"I light up at night. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💡 I glow in the dark."},{"text":"🌌 You can usually see me during the summer."},{"text":"🪲 I'm a type of beetle."}],"options":[{"label":"A Glow Worm","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Firefly","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Lightning Bug","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"bug","question":"I march in lines and live in a colony. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐜 I carry food back to my home."},{"text":"🏘️ I live with lots of my friends and family."},{"text":"🐛 Some people think I am a pest at picnics."}],"options":[{"label":"A Termite","isCorrect":false},{"label":"An Ant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Beetle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"bug","question":"I am a bug that can be green or brown and I blend in with the leaves and sticks. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌿 My body looks like a branch."},{"text":"🌳 I am good at camouflage."},{"text":"🍃 I eat plants."}],"options":[{"label":"A Praying Mantis","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Stick Bug","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Leaf Bug","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"bug","question":"I am a bug that can destroy wood and build complex homes underground. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐛 I like to eat wood structures."},{"text":"🏘️ We live in large colonies."},{"text":"🔥 Sometimes people think of us when buildings collapse"}],"options":[{"label":"A Cockroach","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Termite","isCorrect":true},{"label":"An Earwig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"bug","icon":"🌍"}}],"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I have wheels and carry people, but I'm not a car. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏫 I take you to school."},{"text":"🛑 I stop at designated spots."},{"text":"🎫 You usually need a ticket to ride me."}],"options":[{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I float on water and carry people or things. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I need a big body of water to move."},{"text":"⚓️ I often visit ports."},{"text":"🛳️ I can be big or small, fast or slow."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ship","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly in the sky but have no wings. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚀 I go very high."},{"text":"👨‍🚀 People can travel in me to space."},{"text":"🔥 I use powerful engines to move."}],"options":[{"label":"Kite","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you use your feet to move me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏞️ I'm great for riding in the park."},{"text":"⛑️ You should wear a helmet when using me."},{"text":"⚙️ I might have gears to make pedaling easier."}],"options":[{"label":"Motorcycle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Skateboard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I run on tracks, but I'm not a train. I often go underground. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚇 I help people get around big cities."},{"text":"🗺️ You can use a map to find my stations."},{"text":"⚡ I usually use electricity to move."}],"options":[{"label":"Tram","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Subway","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Monorail","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I’m a vehicle with a long neck that helps put out fires. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚒 I am red."},{"text":"🚨 I have a siren."},{"text":"💧 I spray water."}],"options":[{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fire Truck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Police car","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I have wings, but I don't flap them. I take people to far away places. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"✈️ I fly very high in the sky."},{"text":"🌍 I can take you to different countries."},{"text":"💺 I have seats for many passengers."}],"options":[{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Glider","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I have a sail, but I'm not a sailboat. I can glide across the snow. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"❄️ I am used in snowy regions."},{"text":"🐕‍🦺 I am pulled by animals"},{"text":"🛷 I'm similar to a sled."}],"options":[{"label":"Dogsled","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snowmobile","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Skis","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I move on water, but I don't have a motor or sails. People use paddles to move me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🛶 I'm long and narrow."},{"text":"🏞️ I'm often used on lakes or rivers."},{"text":"🚣 You need to use both arms to control me."}],"options":[{"label":"Ferry","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Kayak","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Raft","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I have a powerful engine and carry heavy things, but I'm not a truck or a train. I help build things. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚧 You often see me at construction sites."},{"text":"🚜 I have a large bucket in the front."},{"text":"🧱 I can move dirt and rocks."}],"options":[{"label":"Bulldozer","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Crane","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Tractor","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚂"}}]}